&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我认为JavaScript可以分为三个核心，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I believe JavaScript can be divided into three cores,
如果你愿意的话，有三根柱子。
three pillars if you will.
这三个支柱绝对是至关重要的
And those three pillars are absolutely critical for
你将要做的所有JavaScript编码，
all of the JavaScript coding that you will ever do,
即使它有品牌名称react或品牌名称Vue.js或品牌棱角。
even if it has the brand name React or the brand name Vue.js or the brand Angular.
你猜怎么着？
Guess what?
甚至对像我这样的老校友来说，
Or even for the old school folks like me,
即使它是jQuery，它仍然是JavaScript，好吗？
even if it's jQuery it's still JavaScript, okay?
而这些东西仍然是基于相同的基本支柱。
And those things are still based upon the same fundamental pillars.
我看到开发人员总是缠绕着自己，扭曲着自己
And I see developers all the time, winding themselves and contorting themselves
围绕着他们特定框架内的所有类型的怪异或
around all kinds of certain weirdness within their particular framework or
不管他们在做什么。
utility whatever it is they're working on.
结果是他们不理解其中一根柱子，或者
And it turns out it's they don't understand one of the pillars, or
其中一根柱子的一部分。
some part of one of these pillars.
本课程旨在解决这个问题。
And this course aims to fix that.
我有一个疯狂的想法，如果你出于什么原因选择了你
I have this crazy notion that if for whatever reason you've chosen you
要让您的职业成为一名JavaScript开发人员，如果您选择了
to make your career be a JavaScript developer, if you've chosen to
为了获得写JavaScript的报酬，你应该理解你的工具。
get paid to write JavaScript, you oughta understand your tool.
那么我们要怎么看这三根柱子呢？
So what are we going to look at those three pillar?
这些柱子中的第一个可能是最不受欢迎的
The first of those pillars may be the least popular of them actually definitely
其中最不受欢迎的，没有人喜欢谈论类型和
the least popular of them, nobody likes to talk about types and
特别是在像JavaScript这样的动态类型语言中，
especially within a dynamically typed language like JavaScript,
这是一个禁忌话题。
this is one of those taboo topics.
如果你跟随道格·克罗克福德，他会告诉你不要使用这些东西
If you follow a Doug Crockford, he tells you don't use any of this stuff don't
当然，想想这些事情中的任何一个，这实际上是不实际的。
think about any of these things of course, that isn’t actually practical.
我们将讨论为什么你应该关心类型。
And we're gonna talk about why you should care about types.
但我还是会在这里说漏嘴的。
But I will just go ahead and spill the beans here.
这个特别的核心对于这个特别的单位的意义是，
The takeaway from this particular core for this particular unit is,
你写代码是不负责任的
it is irresponsible of you to write code and
不理解语言的这个关键事实，好吗？
not understand this critical fact of the language, okay?
说，好吧，有些好的部分告诉我要避免这样做是不负责任的
It is irresponsible to say, well, some good parts told me to just avoid that
话题，不要学，不用担心。
topic, don't learn it, don't need to worry about it.
这是人们在代码中产生bug的主要原因之一。
That is one of the big reasons why people produce bugs in their code.
他们写代码，但他们不理解他们正在写的代码，好吗？
They write code and they don't understand the code that they're writing, okay?
所以我们将涵盖类型，特别是强制系统。
So we're gonna cover the types and specifically the coercion system.
现在，我要求对此持开放的态度，因为我知道你一直如此
Now, I'm gonna ask to have an open mind on it because I know you have been so
被编程认为我们不需要做这些事情，我们应该只是
programmed to think that we don't need to do these things, we should only just
使用三等号，如果我们使用三等号，谁还需要关心呢？
use the triple equals, and who needs to care about it if we use the triple equals?
这不是编写JavaScript的实用方法。
That is just not a practical way of writing JavaScript.
你一直过得很好，但效果不好。
You've been getting by, and it's not effective.
所以当我告诉你的时候，我会要求你有一个开放的心态，也许更开放一些
So I'm gonna ask you to have an open mind when I tell you, and maybe more so
比以往任何时候，我都会有一个非常强烈的，
than I have ever before, I'm gonna have a very strong,
我要坚定地把我的脚踩在你应该是什么的位置上
I'm gonna firmly plant my foot in a position here about what you should be
使用强制执行时，您应该使用JavaScript的类型系统进行操作。
doing with coercion, what you should be doing with JavaScript's type system.
在过去，我有一些观点，就像是好吧，你自己做吧
In the past I've sort of have views that were kind of like well just make your own
一些决定，但我开始相信，我的观点发生了转变
sorts of decisions but I have come to believe, my views have shifted and
我必须相信有一个正确的方式来思考这个问题
I have to come believe there is a correct way to think about this and
我们还没到那一步。
we're not getting there yet.
作为一个社区，我们还没有做到这一点。
We're not there yet as a community.
所以我们在这门课上可以做的最重要的事情之一就是
So maybe one of the most important things we can do in this course is
告诉你为什么这很重要好吗？
enlighten you to why that's so important okay?
我们将要讨论的第二个核心单元是示波器系统。
The second core unit that we're going to talk about is the scope system.
词汇范围，引导我们讨论闭包和
Lexical scopes which leads us into discussions about closure and
最终是模块化模式。
eventually the modular pattern.
这是语言的重要支柱。
This is a critical pillar of the language.
几乎所有其他东西都是建立在它之上的。
Almost everything else is built upon it.
第三个支柱是客体系统。
And the third of the pillars is the objects system.
我喜欢把这称为面向对象，有点不同于
I like to refer to this as the objects oriented, a little bit different than
面向对象，实际上是面向类的。
object oriented, which is actually class oriented.
我们需要了解JavaScript的对象系统是如何工作的，
We need to understand how JavaScript's objects system works,
其中包括this关键字，这个完全令人困惑的东西
which includes the this keyword, that completely befuddling thing that's
实际上，一旦你被教会了它的作用，就会变得非常直截了当。
actually very straightforward once you've been taught what it does.
一旦你脱离了它在其他语言中的作用
Once you disconnect from what it does in other languages and
您将了解它在JavaScript中的作用，它非常简单。
you learn what it does in JavaScript, it's very straightforward.
所以对我们来说理解这三个核心是很重要的。
So it's important for us to understand all three of these cores.
当我们深入研究这个
And when we dig into this and
然后我们深入研究原型，你必须先了解这些东西，然后才能
then we dig into the prototypes, you have to understand that stuff before you can
了解某人在顶部分层的语法糖分，如class关键字。
understand somebody layering on top a syntactic sugar like the class keyword.
我没有在网上隐藏我关于class关键字的想法和选项
I have not hidden my thoughts and options online about the class keyword and
我再告诉你一次，我坚信它不应该在JavaScript中使用。
I will tell you again I firmly believe that it should not be used in JavaScript.
但我说你不应该用它和
But there is a difference between me saying, you shouldn't use it and
我说你不应该学。
me saying you shouldn't learn it.
你绝对应该学习这个系统。
You absolutely should learn this system.
你绝对必须学习这个支柱才能理解为什么
You absolutely must learn this pillar to understand why that particular
编码风格不适合JavaScript，顺便说一句，要理解，
coding style doesn't fit with JavaScript and to understand, by the way,
如果你是被迫做的，怎么做得这么好，
if you are forced to do it, how to do so well,
如果框架为您做出了选择，他们中的许多人都做了。
if that framework makes that choice for you and many of them have.
你还能有效率吗？或者你只是要戴着眼罩编写代码？
Can you still be effective or you're simply gonna be coding with blinders on?
这是JavaScript语言的三大核心支柱
So these are the three core pillars of the JavaScript language and
基本上所有这些柱子都在10天结束时就位
largely all of these pillars were in place at the end of the 10 day
布伦达和我在1995年举行的原型会议。
prototyping session that Brenda and I put back in in 1995.
这在很大程度上是我们已经使用了24年的JavaScript。
This is largely the JavaScript that we've had now for 24 years.
是的，肯定有不同的细节。
Yes, there are definitely different details.
但这些事情中的许多都是核心和
But many of these things are as core and
基础的根，因为它在语言中。
root of a foundation as it gets in the language.
在本课程结束时，它将涵盖大约两天的时间，
At the end of this course which will cover over a period of about two days,
感觉就像我们刚过了五个月或者
it's going to feel a lot more like we just went over five or
十天的材料，因为它是非常压缩的。
ten days worth of material because it's extremely compressed.
所以我不是想让你在这门课结束时说，啊哈，我有资格，
So I don't mean for you to come at the end of this course and say, aha I'm certified,
我知道关于JavaScript的一切，这不是结束，但是
I know everything there is to know about JavaScript, this is not the end but
为什么的开始
the beginning of what for
我已经花了20年的时间来理解JavaScript。
me has been over a 20 year journey to understand JavaScript.
我正在为你记录我对地图的理解。
And I'm documenting for you what I've figured out about the map.
我试着为我的旅途拼凑出一张藏宝图。
I've tried to put together a treasure map for my journey.
我为你们记录了这一点，这也是书的内容。
And I'm documenting that for you, that's also what the books are.
所以在这里用它们作为伴侣。
So use those as companions here.